http://www.opticon.com/privacy-policy

Privacy & Cookie PolicyPrivacy & Cookie Policy Opticon Sensors Europe B.V.Opticon Sensors Europe BV (hereinafter: “Opticon”) recognizes the valuable need to protect the information gathered from our customers and visitors; for this reason, Opticon has implemented a Privacy and Cookie Policy (hereinafter: “Privacy Policy”).Privacy Policy Introduction This Privacy Policy explains the types of personal information we collect from and about you and how we use, disclose and protect that information as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. This Privacy Policy applies to all information gathered through any website or mobile application (hereinafter: “Services”) operated by or on behalf of Opticon. We recommend you to read this Privacy Policy so that you understand our approach towards the use of your personal information. If you do not agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in this way, please do not use our Services or otherwise provide us with your personal information.What is Personal Information?  Personal information means information or pieces of information that could allow you to be identified. Personal information shall include but is not limited to: name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. Opticon will never collect “sensitive” personal information such as information pertaining to racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs, health, and sexual orientation.What Personal Information do we Collect?  Opticon collects personal information about you from a variety of sources, such as:Information Opticon collects directly from you This is the personal information you provide Opticon when using our Services. For example when you create an account or when you purchase a service from us. This type of information may include your (user) name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing information and other content you submit to our websites and any other information you provide voluntarily to us.Information Opticon collects from you when using our services  Opticon may use cookies and similar technologies to collect information when using our Services. This type of information may include your type of browser or device, details of the web pages you have viewed, links you clicked on, your IP address, and any other information you choose to share. For more information on cookies and how to manage them, please see our Cookie Policy.When you download our application to your mobile device we may also collect information that you provide for example when you request information. We also automatically collect information through our Services. This type of information may include advertising ID or a similar identifier, information about your mobile operating system and the way you use the application. Furthermore, our mobile applications may collect information about your actual location from your device if you consent to the collection of this information.Information Opticon collects from other sources Opticon may collect information from other sources if you have given permission for that information to be shared. For example information from public databases and marketing companies. This type of information may include your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, household information, consumer and market research data, purchase behaviour and preferences and information about your lifestyle, such as your hobbies and interests.How We Use Your Personal Information  Opticon uses the personal information it collects from customers as part of its customer database and to provide customers with targeted information and offers. Opticon may use your personal information to operate its various Services, for Opticon specific customer research, to fulfill purchases by you, to provide any other services you have requested, to address quality complaints that you submit, and to provide online product support. Your personal information also may be used to communicate with you regarding your account(s) with Opticon. We also may use your e-mail address to respond to incoming service and support requests from you, to collect customer feedback, to conduct satisfaction surveys, to offer promotions to you, and to send other service informational mailings. Your personal information may be provided to a courier or freight forwarder in order to fulfill an order you may have requested from Opticon.Disclosure of Your Information  Except as described in this Privacy Policy, Opticon will not disclose your personal information to a third party, unless you request or otherwise consent to such disclosure or disclosure is required or authorized by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Opticon or its Services; (b) protect or defend the rights or property of Opticon, its Services or users of the Services or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Opticon, its Services or the public. Opticon also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party (including outside counsel) in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, or financing of all or any portion of Opticon or of any of the business or assets or shares of Opticon or a division thereof in order for you to continue to receive the same products and services from the third party. We would require from the third party to treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Sharing of Personal Information  Personal information may be shared with Opticon affiliates pursuant to the service contracts between them to better service Opticon’s customers. However, any affiliates with whom your personal information is shared will be subject to agreements to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information.Aggregate Information  To measure our visitors’ interest in and use of various areas of our Services and the various programs that we administer, we will rely upon aggregate information, which is information that does not identify you, such as statistical and navigational information. With this aggregate information, we may undertake statistical and other summary analyses of our visitors’ behavior and characteristics. Although we may share this aggregate information with third parties, none of this information will allow anyone to identify you, or to determine anything else personal about you.Storage of Personally Identifiable Information  Your personal information may be transferred, stored and processed in the Netherlands or any other country in which Opticon (or its affiliates, subcontractors or agents) maintain facilities. The laws of these countries may not afford the same level of protection to your personal information. By using our Services or otherwise providing Opticon with personal information, you agree to us doing so in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Where necessary, Opticon will ensure that adequate safeguards are in place to comply with the requirements for the international transfer of personal information under applicable privacy laws.Security The collection, use and disclosure of personal information collected through our Services is safeguarded by technological and organisational security measures with the objective to protect the personal information against loss, misuse and unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. These measures are continually improved in line with technological developments.In particular: (i) we encrypt many of our Services using SSL (ii) we review our information collection, storage and processing practices, from time to time to guard our systems against unauthorized access, and (iii) we restrict access to personal information to our employees and all other parties we work with, who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.We will not retain your personal information for a period longer than necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it was collected for, unless we have to keep it for legitimate business, tax or legal purposes.Your Privacy Rights You are entitled to know whether we hold personal information about you and, if we do, to have a copy of that information. Furthermore, you have the right to data portability and you can request Opticon to correct, update or delete your personal information in our records and/or inform us about any misuse of your personal information. In the case of electronic direct marketing, Opticon will provide you with a method to opt out of receiving further marketing materials or with a method to opt in. You can also delete or change the privacy settings of your account by logging in to your account and accessing your “personal settings”. You can opt-out of the collection of your personal information by our mobile application by deleting the application entirely from your device. To uninstall the application you should use the standard uninstall process of your mobile device. However, please note that Opticon will retain any previous usage information collected from the application for legitimate business purposes, such as to ensure of proper functioning of our Services. Should you need to change or remove your user name or password, contact us through the website form posted on www.opticon.com or directly as further outlined below. If we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.We encourage you to keep your personal settings and personal information at all times current and complete.Accuracy of Personal Information  We take all reasonable steps to insure that your personal information is accurate, up-to-date, complete and relevant.Access and Rectification  Upon written request, Opticon will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information and will give you access to that information. When requesting access to your personal information, we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide the personal information that we hold about you. Opticon aims to keep the personal information as accurate and up-to-date as possible. If you would like to correct, update or delete the personal information you have supplied to Opticon, please contact us as set out below.Third Party Web Sites  For your convenience, we may include on our Services certain links to other websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected, used and restored in connection with the use of our Services. We have structured our Services to make it reasonably clear when you leave our Services and enter another website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of each website you visit through our links, to ensure you are comfortable with their policies.Children  Children under 16 years of age are required to obtain the express permission of a parent or guardian before submitting any personal information to the Services. We encourage parents to supervise their children while online. Cookie Policy Introduction Opticon uses cookies to learn more about the way you interact with our content and to help us to improve your experience when visiting our Services.
What are Cookies? A cookie is a small data file that your browser places on your computer or mobile device. The next time you visit the same website, cookies ensure that your device is recognised. They are used for several different reasons, such as: • Remembering your preferences • Providing you with content tailored to your interests • Assessing how our website is used to improve the overall user experienceCookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer when you have gone offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.The Different Types of Cookies Cookies can be categorised by the role they fulfil on our website: • Functional cookies are essential in order to enable you to use and move around our website and to ensure that our website functions properly. • Analytical cookies are used to collect information on visitor behaviour (e.g. the pages you view most often) to optimise the usability of the website.Unforeseen Cookies Because of how the internet and how websites work, it’s possible that we may have missed a cookie that is placed by a third party on our website. If you happen to find one that isn’t listed above, then please let us know.How do I Reject and Delete Cookies  You can use the settings within your browser to control the cookies that are set on your computer or mobile device. To learn more, please look at the cookie settings available in your specific web browser(s). The links below will take you directly to your browser’s manual. • Google Chrome • Firefox • Internet Explorer • SafariYou may also visit www.youronlinechoices.eu for details on how to remove cookies of specific parties and for further information on cookies generally. However, please be aware that cookies are important to many aspects of the website. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to enjoy all of the features of the website.Modifications Opticon will update this Privacy Policy occasionally. When Opticon posts changes to this Privacy Policy, we also will revise the “last updated” date on the Privacy Policy. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy, Opticon will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Services. Opticon encourages you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to be informed of how Opticon is protecting your personal information and to be aware of any changes to the Privacy Policy. The new Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting. By continuing to access the Services, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.Law and Jurisdiction This Privacy Policy shall only be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the Netherlands. All disputes arising out of or in connection with this Privacy Policy shall be exclusively submitted to a competent court in the Netherlands.Contact Information  If you have any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to access, correct, update, delete or have your personal information transferred, please contact privacy@opticon.com.Complaints Any complaints about the processing of personal data can be submitted to the Dutch Data Protection Authority. You can find more information about filing a complaint at the website of the Dutch Data Protection Authority (https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl).This Privacy & Cookie Policy was last updated on June 17, 2019.Get in Touch!Name*CompanyPhone*Email* Select an Opticon Office*Select an Opticon OfficeAustralia - Opticon Sensors Pty. Ltd.Brazil - Opticon Latin AmericaChina - Opticon Trading Shanghai Co., Ltd.Denmark - Opticon Danmark ApSFrance - Opticon S.A.S.U.Germany - Opticon Sensoren GmbHItaly - Opticon S.R.L.Japan - OPTO Electronics Co., LtdKorea - Opticon Korea Ltd.Malaysia - Opticon Malaysia Sdn. Bhd.Mexico - Opticon Inc.Netherlands - Opticon Sensors Europe BVNorth America - Opticon Inc.Philippines - Opticon Sensors Philippines Inc.Spain - Opticon S.A.S.U.Sweden - Opticon Sensors Nordic ABTaiwan - Opticon Sensors Europe BV Taiwain BranchUK - Opticon LimitedVietnam - Opticon Vietnam LLCCountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiNorth KoreaSouth KoreaKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSudanSudan, SouthSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.YemenZambiaZimbabweYour Question*Subscribe me to the Opticon Newsletter
DisclaimerTerms & ConditionsPrivacy Policy © 2020 Opticon Sensors Europe B.V. | Barcode Scanning & Display Solutions | CoC of Amsterdam No. 34064005 |
VAT No. NL008701325B01 Request a Callback
Please leave your contact information with your question and we will come back to you as soon as possible.Name*E-mail* CompanyCountry*Select a countryAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarrussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwePhone*Your QuestionCAPTCHANewsletter Subscribe me to the Opticon Newsletter* I agree to the privacy policy.*
Leave a message
Leave a message and we will come back to you as soon as possible with a response.Name*E-mail* CompanyCountry*Select a countryAfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarrussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweYour QuestionNewsletter Subscribe me to the Opticon Newsletter* I agree to the privacy policy.*
Questions? Please leave a message and we will come back to you shortly.
Opticon
Scanning SolutionsOEM & Fixed Mount2D CMOS imager-based modulesCCD based modulesLaser based enginesFixed mount scanners BackHandheld ScannersCompanion ScannersCabled ScannersWireless Scanners BackMobile ComputersAndroid Mobile ComputersProprietary Mobile ComputersWindows Mobile Computers Back BackDisplay SolutionsElectronic Shelf LabelsFull Color DisplaysMountingCommunication BackMarketsPostalRetailLogisticsTicketingHospitalityHealthcareIndustrialOther BackService & SupportContact SupportProduct WarrantyConfigure ScannerDownloads BackOur StoryAbout UsJoin the TeamUpcoming EventsLatest News BackHow to Buy
By continuing to use the site, you agree to the use of cookies. more information AcceptThe cookie settings on this website are set to "allow cookies" to give you the best browsing experience possible. If you continue to use this website without changing your cookie settings or you click "Accept" below then you are consenting to this.Close
